{
    "id": "88917bdeb9c54ed6b80dbb13bc349ec0",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The cat is ……………………… the table.",
            "description": "Use on to indicate position on the surface. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I met him ……………………….. the morning.",
            "description": "Use in with morning, evening etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We met ………………………. a wet Friday.",
            "description": "Use on with days.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We can meet …………………… lunchtime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Add a little more milk ……………………… the tea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We can go ……………………….. bus or train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She put the coins …………………….. a box.",
            "description": "In shows position inside. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Birds live ………………………. nests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured man was taken …………………………. hospital.",
            "description": "To indicates direction.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Dad was angry when I failed ……………………….. my test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is rude ………………………… everyone.",
            "description": "We use to with expressions like rude, kind, polite, nice, good etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you yelling ………………………….. me?",
            "description": "We stare, yell, shout or look at someone. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}